Guide to the Richard Pollay Acme Advertising Collection, 1850s-2006 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 7: Acme Beer, 1912-2004 and undated
  - 100-07-063. Acme Brewing Company. Acme Beer newspaper advertisement, 1915 (Box 38)
    At this sign you'll find ACME BEER the beer good taste demands.
  - 100-07-064. Acme Brewing Company. Acme (beer) newspaper advertisement series, 1920 (Box 38)
    Cartoon images to convey: ...for every occasion...for the downtown treat...healthful says the doctor...Brings that satisfying feeling. Each suggests: Order a case from your dealer. Paper is yellowing and fragile.
  - 100-07-065. Acme Brewing Company. Acme Bock Beer cigarette case, undated (Box 13)
    Silver cigarette case with lighter. Empty. Front and back of case feature colored Acme Bock Beer logo with the two-horned ram. Text includes: Brewed and bottled by Acme Brewing Company, Los Angeles, Calif. Case in excellent condition.
  - 100-07-066. Acme Brewing Company. Acme Bock Beer button, undated (Box 13)
    Button shows colored logo of Acme Bock Beer--the two-horned ram on the crest with bunches of grapes in the background. Text is fuzzy and faded: Brewed and bottled by Acme Brewing Company, Los Angeles, Calif. Excellent condition.
  - [Image only] 100-07-067. Cereal and Fruit Products, Ltd. Acme Beer refrigerator magnet, undated (Box 13)
    One round, laminated refrigerator magnet from Acme Beer. Text in red against pale orange background: Enjoy Acme Beer. Cereal and Fruit Products, Ltd. Honolulu, Hawaii. Refrigerator made in USA by Absorbo (?) Beer Pad Company, N.Y.
  - [Image only] 100-07-068. Acme Breweries. Acme Beer button, undated (Box 13)
    One button with text It's the age of Acme, Fine beer since 1860. Acme Breweries. San Francisco. Button in excellent condition.
  - 100-07-069. Grace Bros. Brewery Company. Acme Beer label, undated (Box 38)
    Paper label in gold and blue with blue lions and gold grape leaves. Text around the logo includes Brewed from an old world formula. Packed by Grace Brothers Brewing Company, Santa Rosa, California. Label in excellent condition. Taped on back is a price sticker marked 1. 00.
  - 100-07-070. Acme Breweries. Acme Beer refrigerator magnets (3), undated (Box 38)
    Three colored refrigerator magnets from Acme Beer; one is a reproduction of an Acme magazine advertisement, the second is taken from the beer label and the third features an Acme beer in a can. All in excellent condition.
  - 100-07-071. Acme Breweries. Acme Ale mounted advertisement, 1966 (Box 13)
    Colored reproduction of advertisement mounted on a wooden plaque; artwork is by Maynard Dixon, 1966. Advertisement shows a cowboy riding a horse; words Acme Ale beside a bottle of EnglishTown Acme Ale. Advertisement is torn in several places and stained.
  - 100-07-072. Acme Beer. Acme Beer button, undated (Box 38)
    Button showing the Acme Beer truck with Happy days are here again sign on the back of the truck. Image probably from the Depression period, when the song Happy days was popular. Item in excellent condition.
  - [Image only] 100-07-073. Acme Breweries. Acme Beer metal sign, undated (Box 38)
    One metal sign showing a red-haired woman swinging from a rope and holding a glass of beer. Advertisement reads Swing to Acme California Acme pale ale. Black background. Pieces of paper on back of sign. Metal sign in excellent condition.
  - 100-07-074. Acme Beer label, undated (Box 38)
    Paper beer bottle label. Yellow background. Acme California Brown Ale. Unused condition.
  - 100-07-075. Acme Beer label, undated (Box 38)
    Paper beer bottle label. Black background. Acme California Pale Ale Unused condition.
  - 100-07-076. Acme Beer label, undated (Box 38)
    Paper beer bottle label. Red background. Acme California IPA India Pale Ale Unused condition.
  - 100-07-077. Acme Brewing Company. Acme Beer mouse pad, undated (Box 38)
    Computer mouse pad. White background, black and red lettering. Acme Brewing Company--Enjoy Acme Beer--San Francisco, California As new condition. It is likely that this is not a bonafide Acme Beer marketing item; rather the logo was borrowed and used to produce this novelty item.
  - 100-07-078. Acme Brewing Company. Acme Beer shirt transfer, 2000s (Box 38)
    Shirt transfer on letter size paper. Acme Brewing Company--Enjoy Acme Beer It is likely that this is not a bonafide Acme Beer marketing item; rather the logo was borrowed and used to produce this novelty item.
  - 100-07-080. Acme Breweries. Acme Beer print advertisement, 1948? (Box 38)
    Print advertisement cut out of magazine. Enjoy the World's Most Popular Beer--Acme Beer--Acme Breweries Pencil mark on back marks date as 1948.
  - 100-07-081. Acme Brew newspaper advertisement, 1908 (Box 48E)
    Large page of laminated newsprint from the Atlanta Constitution newspaper, March 11, 1908. Contains advertisement for Acme Brew. Acme Brew--A Prohibition Beer--Non-Alcoholic Non-Intoxicating--Acme Brewing Company, Macon, GA Great condition. Laminated.
  - 100-07-082. Acme Brewing Company. Acme Beer can opener, 1935 (Box 13)
    Metal manual can opener. For Opening Acme Beer Keglet. Pat. No. 1,996,550 Vaughan Chicago--Made in U. S. A Surface rust. Patent number search (www.uspto.gov) reveals patent date of April 2 1935.
  - 100-07-083. Acme Beer. Acme California IPA carton, 1998 (Box 13)
    Red cardboard beer carton. Holds six 12 ounce bottles. Acme California IPA--One of the Ten Best Breweries in the World 1998--Handcrafted. Microbrewed.
- Series 8: Warner Brothers Collectibles, 1970-2006 and undated
  - 100-08-001. Action figure, 1993 (Box 15)
    Wile E. Coyote action figure with back firing mallet! Ouch! Produced by Tyco. Ages 4+. Unopened. Includes Wile E. Coyote and Acme Mallet. Plastic figures. Good condition. Figurine measures at: 12 x 6 cm.
  - 100-08-002. Action figure, 1993 (Box 15)
    Road Runner action figure. Produced by Tyco. Ages 4+. Unopened. Plastic figure. Good condition. Figurine measures at: 12 x 11 cm.
  - 100-08-003. Action figure, 1997 (Box 15)
    Road Runner and Wile E. Coyote action figures. With Acme Flight Suit and Rocket, Back pack and Bird Blasting Artillery. Unopened. Plastic figure. Good condition. Figurines measure at: 20 x 16 cm.
  - 100-08-004. Toy, undated (Box 15)
    Wile E. Coyote soft figure with suction cups on hands. Yellow Yikes star attached. Original label attached. An Official Looney Tunes Product. Good condition.
  - 100-08-005. Golf bag, 1994 (Box 15)
    Looney Tunes golf bag. Featuring the fun and practical line of golfing gifts and accessories including golf pegs and golf balls. Includes 4 colored golf pegs and 1 golf ball. Packaging is taped on one side. Torn when opened. Fair condition.
  - 100-08-006. Acme Domestic Life dust pan, undated (Box 15)
    Metal and plastic dust pan with image of Bugs Bunny type character on front. Made by J. E. Reed, USA. Dirty. Detached original card included. Good condition.
  - 100-08-007. Novelty, undated (Box 15)
    Old Fashioned Tin Truck Collection. Est. 1935. Wile E. Coyote's Traveling Gadget Shop Manufacturers of Anything a Coyote Will Ever Need. Red tin truck. Mint condition. Original box.
  - 100-08-008. Acme Animation Factory, 1997 (Box 15)
    Super-Nintendo game. Original Packaging. ...Actually lets you create your own cartoon [Looney Tunes] adventures... Good condition.
  - 100-08-009. Eyeglass case, 1994 (Box 15)
    Silver metal eyeglass case. Looney Tunes characters engraved on case. Acme Optical. Satisfaction Guaranteed. Original packaging. Mint condition.
  - 100-08-010. Tire gauge, 1995 (Box 15)
    Acme Workshop and Tire Gauge. Metal object. Sylvester and Son image on box and reverse of object. Good condition.
  - 100-08-011. Head band, undated (Box 15)
    Acme head band. Acme Sport Collection. Made in Taiwan. Original plastic cover included. Embroidered name and image of Tweety Bird. Stained. Good condition.
  - 100-08-012. Pin, 1993 (Box 15)
    Brass like metal pin of Wile E. Coyote. His main interest in life is fast food. No. 1 Acme customer. Good condition.
  - 100-08-013. Figurine, 1990 (Box 15)
    Looney Tunes Collector Figurine. Produced by Shell Petroleum. Acme rocket attached to Wile's back. Original packaging. Good condition.
  - 100-08-014. Novelty, undated (Box 15)
    Piping Hot Acme Coffee. It's the Aroma. Cloth. Quilted. Color image and text. Image of Sylvester. Original tag attached. Price $3.00. Good condition,.
  - 100-08-015. Towel, 1994 (Box 15)
    Tea Towel. Red. Wile E. Coyote image on towel. Unused. Good condition.
  - 100-08-016. Towel, 1994 (Box 15)
    Tea Towel. Blue. Wile E. Coyote image on towel. Used. Good condition.
  - 100-08-017. Box, 1991 (Box 15)
    2 empty boxes featuring Tiny Tunes cartoon characters. Tiny Tune Adventures Fruit Snack. Yellow box features Acme Acres. Green box features Acme Looniversity. Product is manufactured by T. J. Lipton, Toronto Canada. Good condition.
  - 100-08-018. Towel, 1993 (Box 15)
    Tea towel features Looney Tunes characters. Color images and text. Produced by Acme Homeworks. Staining evident. Good condition.
  - 100-08-019. Novelty, 1991 (Box 15)
    Piping Hot Acme Coffee. It's the Aroma. Cloth. Color image and text. Image of Sylvester. Unused. Good condition.
  - 100-08-020. Jacket, undated (Box 15)
    Child's denim jacket. Embroidered characters on back. Produced by Acme Trading Company. Metal buttons feature Warner Bros. Initials. Good condition.
  - 100-08-021. Tumbler, undated (Box 15)
    Clear drinking glass featuring Tweety Bird image. Drink 5c, Acme Cola, Good for life. Good condition.
  - 100-08-022. Clock, undated (Box 36)
    Acme Fountain Service. Open 24 hours. Plastic clock face. Made in Taiwan. Good condition.
  - 100-08-023. Video, 1991 (Box 15)
    Warner Bros. Home Video. Stephen Speilberg Presents Tiny Toon Adventures. How I spent My Summer Vacation. Color. 80 minutes. VHS. Acme Looniversity. Good condition.
  - 100-08-024. Comic book, 1970 (Box 15)
    Road Runner comic book. Color. Published by Western Publishing Company. Price 50c. Signs of wear. Good condition.
  - 100-08-025. Comic book, 1970 (Box 15)
    Road runner Comic book. Color. Published by Western Publishing Company. Price 60c. Signs of wear. Good condition.
  - 100-08-026. Sticker album, 1991 (Box 15)
    Tiny Toons Collectors Sticker Album. Published by Panini. Sticker packets applied separately. Color. Unused. Good condition.
  - 100-08-027. Advertising pages, 1998 (Box 15)
    3 pages taken from Time Magazine. Each features Wile E. Coyote and Acme. Part of an advertising campaign put forth by Pontiac for the Grand Prix model.
  - 100-08-028. Credit card, 1997 (Box 15)
    Acme frequent Buyer card. The only credit card accepted by acme and endorsed by Wile E. Coyote. Signed by Rick Pollay. Color. Plastic. Good condition.
  - 100-08-029. Boxers, undated (Box 16)
    Boxer shorts featuring Looney Tunes characters. Good condition.
  - 100-08-030. T-shirt, undated (Box 16)
    Acme. The Name You can Trust. T-shirt. Yellowing. Musty smell. Produced by Acme Clothing Company. Fair condition.
  - 100-08-031. T-shirt, 1991 (Box 16)
    Genuine Acme Outfitters. Grey T-shirt with Looney Tunes characters in silhouetted in background. Worn. Fair condition.
  - 100-08-032. Vest, 1994 (Box 16)
    Acme Garage Clothing. Cotton vest. Cloth patches featuring Looney Tunes characters. Good condition.
  - 100-08-033. Sweatshirt, 1994 (Box 16)
    Sweatshirt. Acme Filling Station for the Best Service. Features Looney Tunes characters. Worn. Musty smell. Good condition.
  - 100-08-034. Clothing, undated (Box 16)
    Acme The Name You Can Trust. Embroidered figured from Looney Tunes on belt. Plastic buckles. Metal zippers. Good condition.
  - 100-08-035. Tie, 1994 (Box 16)
    Silk tie featuring Looney Tunes characters. Acme Bowl League Champ Burbank 1950. Made in Korea. Good condition.
  - 100-08-036. Clothing, 1994 (Box 16)
    Acme Trading Company. 100% Genuine Best Quality. Embroidered Looney Tunes characters. Stained. Musty. Fair condition.
  - 100-08-037. Catalog, 1991 (Box 16)
    Inside the New Warner Bros. Gallery. Color images and text. Good condition.
  - 100-08-038. Apron, 1993 (Box 16)
    Cotton apron. Acme Brand Home-style Satisfaction Guarantee. Looney Tunes characters imprinted on fabric. Soiled. Fair condition.
  - 100-08-039. Apron, 1993 (Box 16)
    Cotton apron. Open 24 hours. Acme's Fountain Service. Looney Tunes characters imprinted on fabric. Soiled. Fair condition.
  - 100-08-040. Clothing, undated (Box 16)
    Acme Extreme Sports. Do not wear if allergic to adrenalin. Good condition.
  - 100-08-041. Jacket, undated (Box 16)
    One green, sleeveless, extra small jean jacket, with square leather tag on the hem which reads: Acme Trading Company. Farm implements, We buy, we sell. Brass buttons say LTC Looney Tunes Classics. Tag sewn on jacket is from Looney Tunes Quality Clothing. Back of jacket is machine embroidered design featuring four Looney Tunes characters, a map of the US and The good life, Small town USA, The heart of America, Pop. 143. Made in Thailand.
  - 100-08-042. T-shirt, 1987 (Box 16)
    T-shirt, Acme, the name you can trust White, cotton and polyester, medium T-shirt with picture of Wile E. Coyote falling down with a busted parachute. Tag is from Hanes. Copyright 1987 from Warner Bros. Stains on item.
  - 100-08-043. Acme baseball cap, 1991 (Box 16)
    One white cap with black rim, with machine embroidered Acme and silhouettes of three Looney Tunes characters on the front; on the back is The name you can trust. Tag is from Acme Clothing Company, TM and copyright 1991 with Warner Bros. Severe stains on item.
  - 100-08-044. T-shirt, 1991 (Box 16)
    T-shirt, Acme Extra Special. One white, large T-shirt showing the smiling faces of three Looney Tunes characters behind the Acme trademark 100% genuine, best quality Acme, extra special. Tag shows Acme Clothing Company. TM and copyright 1991 Warner Bros. Inc. T-shirt starting to yellow.
  - 100-08-045. T-shirt, 1991 (Box 16)
    Acme The name you can trust One white, cotton T-shirt, large size, with silk-screened picture of a parachuting Wile E. Coyote. Acme Clothing Company tag. TM and copyright 1991 Warner Bros. Brand new shirt.
  - 100-08-046. T-shirt, 1992 (Box 16)
    The name you can trust White T-shirt, Large-size, with embroidered Acme Trading Company logo at the back and the silhouette of three Looney Tunes characters on front, with The name you can trust. Acme Clothing Company tag; other tag reads: Made in the Philippines. Trademark copyright 1992 with Warner Bros. Stains on item.
  - 100-08-047. Sweatshirt, 1994 (Box 21)
    Green, long sleeved sweatshirt, no specific size; Large silk-screened logo with three Looney Tunes characters, Acme Delivery Company. Please allow 9 months for delivery. Trademark and copyright 1994 Warner Bros. Tag bears name of Looney Tunes.
  - 100-08-048. T-shirt, 1992 (Box 21)
    One white large T-shirt with design on front showing two Looney Tunes characters and the words Acme Looniversity Varsity Squad. Trade mark and copyright 1992 with Warner Bros. Inc. Tag shows logo of Warner Bros. Shirt starting to yellow.
  - 100-08-049. T-shirt, 1994 (Box 21)
    One large, white T-shirt; design covers the sleeves and the front of the shirt and features Looney Tunes characters and the words Acme Construction Company. Back of the shirt shows Bugs Bunny and the logo of Acme Construction Company. Tag is faded and worn-out. TM and Copyright 1994 with Warner Bros. Freeze New York. Shirt starting to yellow.
  - 100-08-050. Shirt, 1996 (Box 21)
    One grey and black cotton shirt, XL, with yellow collar and sleeve edges; rubberized decoration on left breast side of shirt featuring a cartoon character with an explosion in the background; text reads Acme high voltage clothing. Tag shows Warner Bros Studio Store; smaller tag reads Made in Sri Lanka.
  - 100-08-051. Acme pocket watches, undated (Box 21)
    One gold pocket watch with a Looney Tune character Taz and a railroad crossing sign on the cover of the watch. The back of the watch reads Acme Pocket Watches. The watch is richly decorated. The face of the watch shows the Looney Tune character Taz in the center.
  - 100-08-052. O. S. P. Publishing Inc. Bugs Bunny poster, 1993 (Box 48E)
    One poster of Bugs Bunny wearing Acme shoes and sporting a red bandanna pierced bunny ears, eyeglasses, beads, and dreadlocks. Print in one corner reads: Looney Tunes, characters, names are trademarks of Warner Bros. c. 1993. Comes in original mailing tube from Mike Baker in the US; addressed to Rick Pollay; value set at $3.00.
  - 100-08-053. Baseball cap, 1991 (Box 21)
    One green baseball cap with dark blue rim. Acme Clothing Company Acme The brand to trust is embroidered on front of cap. Embroidered on back of cap is Industrial strength and the silhouettes of two Looney Tunes characters. Copyright with Warner Bros. Made in the USA. Evidence of use.
  - 100-08-055. T-shirt, 1996 (Box 21)
    Black cotton T-shirt with color image and text printed on front and back. Front text: Acme Instant Magnetism makes you instantly attractive. No money back guarantee. No trial period. Text on reverse: Caution. Not tested below a 5 mile radius. Clothing tag reads: Warner Bros Studio. Made in USA.
  - 100-08-056. Socks, undated (Box 21)
    Grey socks with black images of Warner Bros cartoon characters woven in black thread into the fabric. Acme is across the bottom of the socks.
  - [Image only] 100-08-057. Acme metal sign, undated (Box 21)
    Heavy metal sign with Acme in raised letters.
  - 100-08-058. Acme Clothing Company. Acme jacket, undated (Box 21)
    One green wool jacket with genuine brown leather sleeves; A sewn on the left front side. Sewn on the back is Acme Trading Company, 100% Genuine, Best Quality with three Looney Tunes characters. Tag is from Acme Clothing Company. TM and Copyright with Warner Bros, Inc. Made in the US. Matching cap is in 100-08-53.
  - 100-08-059. Acme Clothing Company. Denim jacket, 1993 (Box 21)
    One denim and cotton jacket; embroidered on back: Acme Manufacturing Company, Work Force World Wide, Everlasting Construction, An ingenious solution for every problem; at the center is a wheel with the world and stars and the words Industrial Strength. Made in Hong Kong. TM and copyright with Warner Bros. Tag is from Acme Clothing Company. Jacket well-used.
  - 100-08-060. The Acme Catalog novelty book, 2006 (Box 15)
    Soft cover Warner Brothers novelty book. The Acme Catalog--Quality is our #1 Dream--Redefining Pain for Over 60 Years. Mail order catalog of fictional Acme items. As new condition.
  - 100-08-061. Printout of Wikipedia Entry Acme Corporation, 2006 (Box 15)
    Paper printout of the entry Acme Corporation from the online encyclopedia Wikipedia (www.wikipedia.org). Three pages. Accessible on the World Wide Web at:
    Wikipedia Acme entry
    Wikipedia is an online encyclopedia community. Entries can be edited by anyone.
  - 100-08-062. Illustrated Catalog of Acme Products, 2006 (Box 15)
    Printout of the website The Original Illustrated Catalog of Acme Products. Alphabetical listing of Acme products used in Warner Bros. cartoons. Also gives year and title of cartoon where item first appeared. See related item 100-08-60
    Link to Acme Illustrated Catalog site.
  - 100-08-063. Acme Racing decals, undated (Box 15)
    Pair of small decals on paper backing. Acme Racing. Color image of Wile E. Coyote.
  - 100-08-064. Dinner plate, 1993 (Box 36)
    Large dinner plate from the Acme Bar and Grill. Blue lettering on beige background. Blue Plate Special--Acme Bar and Grill--For Family, Friends, and Fun--Burbank, California.
  - 100-08-065. T.N.T. bubblegum balls, 1996 (Box 36)
    Plastic novelty stick of T. N. T. Tube contains gum balls. Tube also emits a sound effect when a button is pressed (3-2-1, noise of explosion).
- Series 9: Clothing Collectibles, 1991-1995 and undated
  - 100-09-001. Acme gloves, undated (Box 17)
    Green nylon gloves, small fake pearl inset in rosettes. Original label attached. Size 6 1/2. Made in Canada. See: Advertisement, 100-16-108.
  - 100-09-002. Acme Plumbing and Heating. Oven mitts, undated (Box 17)
    Oven mitts, quilted, unused, good condition.
  - 100-09-003. Tultex Acme Skateboard T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One brown cotton T-shirt, large size, with blue silk-screened logo Acme Skateboard Quality Since 1991. Tag reads Tultex and assembled in Mexico of USA parts. Text in English, Japanese and Spanish. In excellent condition.
  - 100-09-004. Acme Garage T-shirt, 1994 (Box 17)
    One grey T-shirt, Large size, with embroidered picture of Bugs Bunny and Tazmanian devil in car. Text includes: Acme Garage Drive-Thru Service, Friendly and Efficient. On the boulevard, Burbank, USA. Copyright 1994 Warner Bros. Made in the Philippines.
  - 100-09-005. Fruit of the Loom Acme T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One black, cotton T-shirt, large size, with silkscreened picture of bondage woman and the words Acme. Tag from Fruit of the Loom, made in the USA. Small holes in shirt, worn-out item.
  - 100-09-006. Acme California Pale Ale T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One blue, cotton T-shirt, large size, with silkscreened logo on the front: Acme California Pale Ale. Text in red letters on the back reads: A Tradition Since 1861. Text in English, French and Spanish. Tag reads Gildan Activewear. Assembled in Honduras with Canadian components. Item in excellent condition.
  - 100-09-007. Acme Basketball shirt, undated (Box 17)
    One grey striped shirt. Blue letters. Red embroidered: Acme on sleeve. Good condition.
  - 100-09-008. Acme Oyster House T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One black, cotton Fruit of the Loom T-shirt, XL size, with silkscreened Acme Oyster House on front and back. Item in excellent condition.
  - 100-09-009. Acme Garage T-shirt, 1994 (Box 17)
    One cotton, black and white striped, button up shirt with black sleeves and collar. Acme Garage machine embroidered on left breast pocket. On the back are Looney Tunes characters, the words Acme Garage The Service Your Automobile Deserves. Circular logo with red star and TAZCO at the bottom of the design. Acme Garage Clothing tag, made in Hong Kong. Brand new shirt.
  - 100-09-010. Durham Knitting Mills The earth is your backyard. Greenpeace T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One grey, cotton T-shirt, with silkscreened picture, Roy Lichtenstein style, of toxic waste being dumped by the Acme toxic waste disposal company. Woman screams, Oh no, not in my backyard! Text on bottom of picture: The earth is your backyard. Greenpeace. Tag reads: America's Finest. Durham Knitting Mills.
  - 100-09-011. Acme Bilt Clothing T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One brown striped, cotton T-shirt, medium size, with label Acme Bilt Clothing sewn on breast pocket. Back of clothing tag: Acmebilt is dedicated to making fine skate clothing...Keep skating.
  - 100-09-012. Acme Cat Exterminators T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One white, cotton T-shirt, large size, with Acme machine-embroidered on left breast. A picture of a terrified cat and Acme Cat Exterminators is embroidered on the back. Hanes tag, assembled in Honduras with US made components. Text is in English, Spanish and French. Brand new shirt.
  - 100-09-013. Kent. Acme Food Sales jersey, 1990s (Box 17)
    One blue baseball jersey with Kent Acme Food Sales appliquéd in front. Faded clothing tag. 25 appliquéd on back.
  - 100-09-014. Xcelsior Brewery. Acme Beer T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)
    One yellow, cotton T-shirt, large size, with Acme Beer, Xcelsior Brewery label silkscreened on front. Brewed in Sonoma County. Back of shirt reads: Xcelsior Brewery Santa Rosa California. Anvil clothing tag. Stains on item.
  - 100-09-015. Acme Grill T-shirt, 1990s (Box 17)